{
    "One": {
        "key_message": "You found a itemOne answer the question to collect the item",
        "question": "What is a common symptom of anxiety?",
        "answers": ["Increased appetite", "Restlessness"],
        "correct_answer": "Restlessness"
    },
    "Two": {
        "key_message": "You found a key to the door.",
        "question": "What is a common symptom of depression?",
        "answers": ["Increased energy", "Improved mood", "Loss of interest in activities", "Increased appetite"],
        "correct_answer": "Loss of interest in activities"
    },
    "Three": {
        "key_message": "You found a key to the door.",
        "question": "What is a common symptom of PTSD?",
        "answers": ["Flashbacks", "Nightmares", "Increased appetite", "Improved sleep"],
        "correct_answer": "Flashbacks"
    },
    "Four": {
        "key_message": "You found a key to the door.",
        "question": "What is a common symptom of bipolar disorder?",
        "answers": ["Mood swings", "Increased energy", "Improved focus", "Decreased appetite"],
        "correct_answer": "Mood swings"
    },
    "Five": {
        "key_message": "You found a key to the door.",
        "question": "What is a common symptom of ADHD?",
        "answers": ["Difficulty focusing", "Increased energy", "Improved organization", "Decreased impulsivity"],
        "correct_answer": "Difficulty focusing"
    },
    "Six": {
        "key_message": "You found a key to the door.",
        "question": "What is a common symptom of OCD?",
        "answers": ["Obsessive thoughts", "Compulsive behaviors", "Increased anxiety", "Decreased motivation"],
        "correct_answer": "Obsessive thoughts"
    },
    "Seven": {
        "key_message": "You found a key to the door.",
        "question": "What is a common symptom of schizophrenia?",
        "answers": ["Hallucinations", "Delusions", "Disorganized thinking", "Decreased motivation"],
        "correct_answer": "Hallucinations"
    },
    "Eight": {
        "key_message": "You found a key to the door.",
        "question": "What is a common symptom of borderline personality disorder?",
        "answers": ["Mood swings", "Impulsive behavior", "Fear of abandonment", "Decreased self-esteem"],
        "correct_answer": "Fear of abandonment"
    },
    "Nine": {
        "key_message": "You found a key to the door.",
        "question": "What is a common symptom of narcissistic personality disorder?",
        "answers": ["Grandiosity", "Lack of empathy", "Need for admiration", "Decreased self-confidence"],
        "correct_answer": "Grandiosity"
    },
    "Ten": {
        "key_message": "You found a key to the door.",
        "question": "What is a common symptom of avoidant personality disorder?",
        "answers": ["Social anxiety", "Fear of rejection", "Perfectionism", "Decreased motivation"],
        "correct_answer": "Social anxiety"
    }
}